plus2net.com 2016-03-09

# Privacy Policy of plus2net.com

**Privacy Policy**  
We do not collect your personal information. Your privacy is important to us. 

While visiting this web site to generate statistics we collect your referrer, IP address, browser, pages access, date and time of uses. This information is used for site analysis only to bring improvements in all areas. 

Your submitted information If you choose to write to us with your contact information, we will respond to this and we will not disclose your personal information to third party.   
1\. Electronic newsletters policy (Dispatches)  
We will offer a free electronic newsletter to users. plus2net.com gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration. 

2\. Message boards/forums policy / comment posting  
Users of the site's Message Boards and Forums must register separately for these services (both are free of charge) in order to post messages, although they needn't register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address. While posting comments user has to submit name and email address. Name will be displayed but email address will not be exposed at the public view pages. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf). 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.   
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.   
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

You can [contact us here](http://www.plus2net.com/contactus.php)
